Guide to the New York University Archives Photograph Collection PHOTO.00001
New York University Archives
- University Building, 1832-1894 (Box 246, Folder 1)
  - University Building - Exterior, 1893? (Box 248, Folder 8)
    - University Building, Exterior, 1893?; CB_UB_3_8_01; Negative print, 4 x 4.75 inches. Image is a view looking east with a horse and carriage. (Box 248, Folder 8, Item 1)
  - University Building - Exterior, 1893? "Richard Original" (Box 248, Folder 9)
    - University Building, Exterior, 1893?; CB_UB_3_9_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 7 x 8.75 inches. (Box 248, Folder 9, Item 1)
  - University Building - Exterior, 1894 Snow Scene (Box 248, Folder 10)
    - University Building, Exterior, 1894; CB_UB_3_10_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 7.575 x 9.5 inches. (Box 248, Folder 10, Item 1)
  - University Building - Exterior, 1894? Tower (Box 248, Folder 11)
    - University Building, Exterior, Cecil Dreeme Tower, 1894?; CB_UB_3_11_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 7.5 x 8.5 inches. (Box 248, Folder 11, Item 1)
  - University Building - Exterior 19th Century, Harris, undated (Box 248, Folder 12)
    - University Building, Exterior, undated; CB_UB_3_12_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 7.25 x 7.5 inches. (Box 248, Folder 12, Item 1)
    - University Building, Exterior, undated; CB_UB_3_12_02; black-and-white print (photograph), 8.25 x 7.75 inches. (Box 248, Folder 12, Item 2)
  - University Building - Exterior, undated Montages, N.D. (Box 248, Folder 13)
    - University Building, Exterior, undated; CB_UB_3_13_01; Illustration, 5.5 x 9.5 inches. Image is a montage of smaller illustrations of University Building and Washington Square Park. (Box 248, Folder 13, Item 1)
  - University Building - Exterior, 1894? (Box 248, Folder 16)
    - University Building, Exterior, 1894?; CB_UB_3_16_01; Illustration, 6.5 x 9 inches. Image is a watercolor of Alfred Zucker's University Building. (Box 248, Folder 16, Item 1)
    - University Building, Exterior, 1894?; CB_UB_3_16_02; Illustration, 7.25 x 8.25 inches. Image is a watercolor by G. Welch of Alfred Zucker's University Building. (Box 248, Folder 16, Item 2)
  - University Building - Interior, Chancellor's Office, 1892 (Box 249, Folder 1)
    - University Building, Interior - Chancellor's Room, 1892; CB_UB_4_1_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 4.75 x 6.75 inches. Image is of chancellor's room. (Box 249, Folder 1, Item 1)
      New York University -- Buildings.; MacCracken, Henry Mitchell, 1840-1918
    - University Building, Interior - Chancellor's Room, 1892; CB_UB_4_1_02; Illustration, 7.25 x 9.5 inches. Image is from the publication Frank Leslie's Montly, March 1892. (Box 249, Folder 1, Item 2)
  - University Building - Interior, 1850-1892, Chapel (Box 249, Folder 2)
    - University Building, Interior - Chapel, undated; CB_UB_4_2_01; Illustration 7.5 x 5.25 inches. Image is from unknown publication p. 60. (Box 249, Folder 2, Item 1)
    - University Building, Interior - Chapel, undated; CB_UB_4_2_02; Illustration, 8.5 x 7.375 inches. (Box 249, Folder 2, Item 2)
      Do Not Reproduce - Property of New-York Historical Society (N-YHS).
    - University Building, Interior - Chapel, 1856; CB_UB_4_2_03; Illustration, 7.5 x 8.375 inches. (Box 249, Folder 2, Item 3)
    - University Building, Interior - Chapel, 1850; CB_UB_4_2_04; Illustration, 4.5 x 5.575 inches. (Box 249, Folder 2, Item 4)
      New York University -- Buildings.; Mott, Valentine, 1785-1865; Wainwright, Jonathan Mayhew, 1792-1854
    - University Building, Interior - Chapel, 1850; CB-UB_4_2_05; Illustration, 6 x 8.75 inches. (Box 249, Folder 2, Item 5)
    - University Building, Interior - Chapel, 1892; CB_UB_4_2_06; Illustration, 6 x 9.5 inches. Image is from Frank Leslie's Monthly, March 1892. (Box 249, Folder 2, Item 6)
    - University Building, Interior - Chapel, 1894; CB_UB_4_2_07; Black-and-white print (photograph), 4.575 x 6.75 inches. (Box 249, Folder 2, Item 7)
  - University Building - Interior, Chemistry Lab, ca. 1893 (Box 249, Folder 3)
    - University Building, Interior - Chemistry Lab, 1895; CB_UB_4_3_01; Black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches. (Box 249, Folder 3, Item 1)
      Chemistry.; New York University -- Buildings.
  - University Building - Interior, Council Room, 1894 (Box 249, Folder 4)
    - University Building, Interior - Council Room, 1894; CB_UB_4_4_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 7.5 x 9.5 inches. (Box 249, Folder 4, Item 1)
    - University Building, Interior - Council Room, 1894; CB_UB_4_4_02; Black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches. (Box 249, Folder 4, Item 2)
  - University Building - Interior, Eucleian Hall, 1894 (Box 249, Folder 5)
    - University Building, Interior - Eucleian Hall, 1894; CB_UB_4_5_01; Black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches. (Box 249, Folder 5, Item 1)
  - University Building - Interior, Greek Room, 1894 (Box 249, Folder 6)
    - University Building, Interior - Greek Hall, 1894; CB_UB_4_6_01; Black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches. (Box 249, Folder 6, Item 1)
  - University Building - Interior, Hennessy's Studio, 1866 (Box 249, Folder 7)
    - University Building, Interior - Hennessy's Studio, 1866; CB_UB_4_7_01; Jones, Theodore Francis, 1885-; Illustration, 3.5 x 3.75 inches. Image is from publication "New York University 1832: 1932" by Theodore F. Jones, 1933. (Box 249, Folder 7, Item 1)
  - University Building - Interior, Junior Law Room, 1894 (Box 249, Folder 8)
    - University Building, Interior - Junior Law Room, 1894; CB_UB_4_8_01; Black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches. (Box 249, Folder 8, Item 1)
      New York University -- Buildings.; New York University. School of Law
  - University Building - Interior, Library, 1894 (Box 250, Folder 1)
    - University Building, Interior - Library, 1894; CB_UB_5_1_01; Black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches. (Box 250, Folder 1, Item 1)
      New York University -- Buildings.; New York University. Libraries
  - University Building - Interior, Pedagogy Office, 1894 (Box 250, Folder 2)
    - University Building, Interior - Pedagogy Office, 1894; CB_UB_5_2_01; Black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches. (Box 250, Folder 2, Item 1)
      Pedagogy.; New York University -- Buildings.
    - University Building, Interior - Pedagogy Office -- Negative, 1925 (Item 21)
  - University Building - Interior, Philomathean Hall, 1894 (Box 250, Folder 3)
    - University Building, Interior - Philomathean Hall, 1894; CB_UB_5_3_01; Black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches. (Box 250, Folder 3, Item 1)
  - University Building - Interior, Physics Lab, 1894 (Box 250, Folder 4)
    - University Building, Interior - Physics Lab, 1894; CB_UB_5_4_01; Black-and-white print (photograph), 4.5 x 6 inches. (Box 250, Folder 4, Item 1)
      New York University -- Buildings.; Physics |x Study and teaching |y 19th century.
    - University Building, Interior - Physics Lab, 1894; CB_UB_5_4_02; Black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches. (Box 250, Folder 4, Item 2)
  - University Building - Interior, Plans, 1830s (Box 250, Folder 5)
    - University Building, Interior - Plans, undated; CB_UB_5_5_01; Black-and-white print (photograph), 5.75 x 9 inches. Image is of northwest corner room building plan and interior elevation. (Box 250, Folder 5, Item 1)
      Do Not Reproduce - Property of the Metropolitan Museum of Art.
      New York University -- Buildings.; blueprints (reprographic copies)
    - University Building, Interior - Plans, 1832; CB_UB_5_5_02; negative print, 4 x 4.75 inches. Image is of exterior elevation and building plan of a drawing from Alexander Jackson Davis's diary. (Box 250, Folder 5, Item 2)
    - University Building, Interior - Plans, undated; CB_UB_5_5_03; Black-and-white print (photograph), 6.75 x 8 inches. Image is of Chapel floor plan by Alexander Jackson Davis. (Box 250, Folder 5, Item 3)
  - University Building - Interior, Richards' Studio, 1894? (Box 250, Folder 6)
    - University Building, Interior - Richards' Studio, 1894?; CB_UB_5_6_01; Black-and-white print (photograph), 8.5 x 10 inches. (Box 250, Folder 6, Item 1)
  - University Building - Interior, Small Chapel, 1894 (Box 250, Folder 7)
    - University Building, Interior - Small Chapel, 1894; CB_UB_5_7_01; Black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches. (Box 250, Folder 7, Item 1)
    - University Building Small Chapel - Interior -- Negative, 1894 (Item 23)
- Washington Square Campus Buildings
  - Alumni Hall - Exteriors, 1987-1992 (Box 184, Folder 1)
    - Alumni Hall, circa 1990; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5580; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 184, Folder 1, Item 1)
    - Alumni Hall, circa 1990; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5583; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 184, Folder 1, Item 2)
    - Alumni Hall, circa 1990; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5585; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 184, Folder 1, Item 3)
    - Alumni Hall, circa 1990; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5587; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 184, Folder 1, Item 4)
    - Alumni Hall, circa 1990; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5889; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 184, Folder 1, Item 5)
    - Alumni Hall, circa 1990; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5591; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 184, Folder 1, Item 6)
    - Alumni Hall, circa 1990; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5594; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 184, Folder 1, Item 7)
    - Alumni Hall, circa 1990; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5597; color print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 184, Folder 1, Item 8)
    - Alumni Hall, circa 1990; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5600; color print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 184, Folder 1, Item 9)
    - Alumni Hall, circa 1990; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5602; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 184, Folder 1, Item 10)
    - Alumni Hall, circa 1990; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5604; color print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 184, Folder 1, Item 11)
  - Alumni Hall - Interiors (Box 184, Folder 2)
    - Interior of Alumni Hall, Looking South on 3rd Avenue, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5607; color print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 184, Folder 2, Item 1)
  - ANTA Theater, 1963-1968 (Box 184, Folder 3)
    - ANTA Theater, Looking South, 1968; NYU.ARCH.PHOTO.00001_ref5611; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 184, Folder 3, Item 1)
      New York University -- Buildings.; Theater.
    - ANTA Theater, 1964; NYU.ARCH.PHOTO.00001_ref5613; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 184, Folder 3, Item 2)
    - ANTA Theater, Looking South-West, 1968; NYU.ARCH.PHOTO.00001_ref5615; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 184, Folder 3, Item 3)
    - Floor Plan of the Interior, ANTA Theater, circa 1963; NYU.ARCH.PHOTO.00001_ref5617; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 184, Folder 3, Item 4)
      New York University -- Buildings.; Theater.; Floor plans.
    - Artist's Sketch of the Exterior of the ANTA Theater, circa 1963; NYU.ARCH.PHOTO.00001_ref5619; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 184, Folder 3, Item 5)
      Theater.; New York University -- Buildings.
    - Excavation of Land for the Repertory Theater, 1963; NYU.ARCH.PHOTO.00001_ref5621; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 184, Folder 3, Item 6)
    - ANTA Theater Construction, circa 1963; NYU.ARCH.PHOTO.00001_ref5624; black-and-white print (photograph), 4 x 5 inches (Box 184, Folder 3, Item 7)
    - ANTA Theater Dedication, circa 1963; NYU.ARCH.PHOTO.00001_ref5626; black-and-white print (photograph), 4 x 5 inches (Box 184, Folder 3, Item 8)
    - ANTA Theater Dedication, circa 1963; NYU.ARCH.PHOTO.00001_ref5628; black-and-white print (photograph), 4 x 5 inches (Box 184, Folder 3, Item 9)
    - ANTA Theater Dedication, circa 1963; NYU.ARCH.PHOTO.00001_ref5630; black-and-white print (photograph), 4 x 5 inches (Box 184, Folder 3, Item 10)
    - ANTA Theater Dedication, circa 1963; NYU.ARCH.PHOTO.00001_ref5632; black-and-white print (photograph), 4 x 5 inches (Box 184, Folder 3, Item 11)
    - ANTA Theater Dedication, circa 1963; NYU.ARCH.PHOTO.00001_ref5634; black-and-white print (photograph), 4 x 5 inches (Box 184, Folder 3, Item 12)
    - ANTA Theater Dedication, circa 1963; NYU.ARCH.PHOTO.00001_ref5636; black-and-white print (photograph), 4 x 5 inches (Box 184, Folder 3, Item 13)
    - ANTA Theater Dedication, circa 1963; NYU.ARCH.PHOTO.00001_ref5638; black-and-white print (photograph), 4 x 5 inches (Box 184, Folder 3, Item 14)
    - ANTA Theater Dedication, circa 1963; NYU.ARCH.PHOTO.00001_ref5640; black-and-white print (photograph), 4 x 5 inches (Box 184, Folder 3, Item 15)
    - ANTA Theater Dedication, circa 1963; NYU.ARCH.PHOTO.00001_ref5642; black-and-white print (photograph), 4 x 5 inches (Box 184, Folder 3, Item 16)
    - ANTA Theater Dedication, circa 1963; NYU.ARCH.PHOTO.00001_ref5644 (Box 184, Folder 3, Item 17)
    - Groundbreaking at the ANTA Repertory Theater, circa 1963; NYU.ARCH.PHOTO.00001_ref5645; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 184, Folder 3, Item 18)
    - Aerial view of the ANTA Theater, Looking West, 1964; NYU.ARCH.PHOTO.00001_ref5647; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 184, Folder 3, Item 19)
    - ANTA Theater, Looking South West, 1964; NYU.ARCH.PHOTO.00001_ref5649; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 184, Folder 3, Item 20)
    - ANTA Theater, Looking South East, 1964; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5775; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 184, Folder 3, Item 21)
  - Washington Square Campus Buildings - Architectual Details, Undated (Box 185, Folder 1)
    - University Seal, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5651; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 185, Folder 1, Item 1)
      Architecture.; New York University -- Buildings.
    - Window Grill, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5653; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 185, Folder 1, Item 2)
    - Decorative Stonework, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5655 (Box 185, Folder 1, Item 3)
      General Physical Description note
    - Decorative Stonework, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5658; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 185, Folder 1, Item 4)
      New York University -- Buildings.; Architecture.
    - Decorative Stonework, 19 University Place, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5660; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 185, Folder 1, Item 5)
    - Detail of 721 Broadway, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5662; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 185, Folder 1, Item 6)
    - Door, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5664; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 185, Folder 1, Item 7)
    - Head of Aphrodite, 1974; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5666; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 185, Folder 1, Item 8)
    - Facade Detail with Columns, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5668; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 185, Folder 1, Item 9)
    - Detail of Grill Work, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5670; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 185, Folder 1, Item 10)
    - Decorative Stonework, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5672; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 185, Folder 1, Item 11)
      Architecture.; Historic buildings -- New York (State) -- New York.
    - Stone Lion Statue, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5674; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 185, Folder 1, Item 11a)
    - Detail of a Doric Column, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5676; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 185, Folder 1, Item 12)
    - Detail of Anthemion (Honeysuckle) Pattern, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5678; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 185, Folder 1, Item 13)
    - Stair Railing Balustrade, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5680; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 185, Folder 1, Item 14)
    - Detail of a Doorway Lintel, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5682; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 185, Folder 1, Item 15)
    - Detail of a Doorway Lintel, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5684; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 185, Folder 1, Item 16)
    - Detail of Staircase and Balustrade, Unudated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5686; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 185, Folder 1, Item 17)
    - Decorative Stonework, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5688; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 185, Folder 1, Item 18)
    - Decorative Stonework, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5690; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 185, Folder 1, Item 19)
    - Building Facade, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5692; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 185, Folder 1, Item 20)
    - Detail of a Building Corner with Columns, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5694; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 185, Folder 1, Item 21)
    - Decorative Stonework, Udated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5696; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 185, Folder 1, Item 22)
    - Detail of a Building Facade with Arches, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5698; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 185, Folder 1, Item 23)
    - Stone Lion Statue, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5700; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 185, Folder 1, Item 24)
    - Decorative Stonework, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5702; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 185, Folder 1, Item 25)
    - Anthemion (Honeysuckle) Fence Detail, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5704; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 185, Folder 1, Item 26)
    - Deocrative Stonework, Building Corner Detail, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5706; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 185, Folder 1, Item 27)
    - Detail of a Building Corner with Columns and Arches, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5708; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 185, Folder 1, Item 28)
    - Detail of an Ionic Column, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5710; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 185, Folder 1, Item 29)
    - Detail of a Building Corner, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5712; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 185, Folder 1, Item 30)
    - Detail of a Corinthian Column, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5714; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 185, Folder 1, Item 31)
    - Decorative Stonework, 1984; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5716; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 185, Folder 1, Item 32)
    - Detail of Medal for Distinguished Teaching, Black and White Photograph - 8 x 10 inches (Box 185, Folder 1, Item 31)
    - Detail Garibaldi Statue Head, Black and White (8 x 10) Photograph (Box 185, Folder 1, Item 32)
    - Detail of Washington Square Arch, NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref6000; Black and White (8 x 10) Photograph (Box 185, Folder 1, Item 33)
  - Asbury Methodist Church (Formerly Dutch Reformed Church), circa 1890 (Box 185, Folder 2)
    - Drawing of the Church, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5719; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 185, Folder 2, Item 1)
    - View of the Front Exterior, circa 1890; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ ref5721; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 185, Folder 2, Item 2)
      New York University -- Buildings.; Church buildings.
    - View of the Front Exterior, circa 1890; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5723; black-and-white print (photograph), 6.75 x 9.5 inches (Box 185, Folder 2, Item 3)
      Church buildings.; New York University -- Buildings.
  - Barney Building, 1939-1981 (Box 185, Folder 3)
    - View of the Hebrew Technical Institute (now Barney Building), 34-36 Stuyvesant Street, Looking East, circa 1939; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5726; black-and-white print (photograph), 6.75 x 8.25 inches (Box 185, Folder 3, Item 1)
      New York University. Real Estate.; New York University -- Buildings.
    - Lebost Wind Turbine (Windmill), Roof of the Barney Building, 1979; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5729; black-and-white print (photograph), 6 x 8.5 inches (Box 185, Folder 3, Item 2)
      New York University -- Buildings.; Windmills.
    - Lebost Wind Turbine (Windmill), Roof of the Barney Building, 1979; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5731; black-and-white print (photograph), 6 x 8.5 inches (Box 185, Folder 3, Item 3)
    - Lebost Wind Turbine (Windmill), Roof of the Barney Building, 1980; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5733; New York University. Office of Public Affairs; black-and-white print (photograph), 4 x 5 inches (Box 185, Folder 3, Item 4)
    - Dedication of the Lebost Wind Turbine (Windmill) atop of the Barney Building, 1980; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5736; black-and-white print (photograph), 4.75 x 6.75 inches (Box 185, Folder 3, Item 5)
      Windmills.; New York University -- Buildings.
    - Solar Collectors, Rood of the Barney Building, 1981; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5738; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 185, Folder 3, Item 6)
      Solar energy; New York University -- Buildings.
  - Benedick Building, circa 1914-1916 (Box 185, Folder 4)
    - Benedick Building, 80 Washington Square East, circa 1915; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5741; black-and-white print (photograph), 3.5 x 5.5 inches (Box 185, Folder 4, Item 1)
      New York University. Real Estate.; New York University -- Washington Square Campus.; New York University -- Buildings.
    - Students' Building, Benedick Building, 80 Washington Square East, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5743; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 185, Folder 4, Item 2)
  - Benedick Building, Room 59, Department of Business Education, Undated (Box 185, Folder 4)
    - Room 59, Department of Business Education, Benedick Building, 80 Washington Square East, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5746; black-and-white print (photograph), 6.25 x 9.25 inches (Box 185, Folder 4, Item 1)
      New York University -- Buildings.; Business Education
  - Bobkin Lane, circa 1938-1990 (Box 186, Folder 1)
    - Bobkin Lane, Looking North, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5749; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 186, Folder 1, Item 1)
      New York University -- Washington Square Campus.; New York University -- Buildings.
    - Bobkin Lane, Looking South, circa 1982; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5751; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 186, Folder 1, Item 2)
    - Bobkin Lane, Site of Elmer Holmes Bobst Library, Wooster Street and Washington Square South, circa 1938; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5755; black-and-white print (photograph), 4.5 x 6.5 inches (Box 186, Folder 1, Item 4)
    - Varsity Luncheon, Bobkin Lane, Site of Elmer Holmes Bobst Library, West Side of Wooster Street, Looking South from West 4th Street, 1945; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5757; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 186, Folder 1, Item 5)
      New York University -- Buildings.; New York University -- Washington Square Campus.
    - Fair, Bobkin Lane, 1974; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5759; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 186, Folder 1, Item 6)
    - Bobkin Lane, Looking South, 1982; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5761; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 186, Folder 1, Item 7)
    - Installation, Bobkin Lane, Looking North, circa 1982; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5673; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 186, Folder 1, Item 8)